Yosano is a quiet girl who moves to Tokyo to live with her uncle.
The moment she gets there, she sees a shooting star and faints from the shock.
Right before she hits the ground, a mysterious hand catches her.
Turns out, that hand belongs to a pretty unusual guy.
At first, he doesn't seem like a big deal.
Until the next day, when Yosano spots him at school and realizes he's Shishio,
her teacher, underneath his quirky hat, he's actually super handsome.
And he's not just there to teach her history.
He's about to teach her what it means to fall in love.
But Shishio isn't the only one catching her attention.
There's also Mamora, a good-looking classmate who lets her borrow his notes,
but gets all flustered and annoyed whenever she touches him.
And she has no clue why.
One day, overwhelmed, Yosano escapes to the rooftop.
There, Shishio gets so close that she swears she can see stars reflected in his eyes.
He tells her she should try making some friends, so Yosano decides to get closer to Mamora.
But he brushes her off, until she accidentally touches him and he turns bright red.
Turns out, he's just super shy around girls.
After Yosano discovers his little secret, Mamora starts opening up to her.
And the two of them end up becoming friends.
Yosano is thrilled.
But their new friendship catches everyone off guard.
Especially Yuyuka, who secretly has feelings for Mamora and is totally jealous of how close they've gotten.
So, during a school trip, Yuyuka tricks Yosano into going to a random cabin deep in the woods.
As you'd expect, Yosano gets lost.
But Mamora shows up, willing to do whatever it takes to find her.
It's like Yosano's perfume is guiding him.
Or maybe it's just his heart leading the way.
Mamora opens up, telling Yosano that he's shy because his mom abandoned him when he was a kid.
It eats him up inside, especially since he doesn't want to be that way around her.
Honestly, when she falls asleep on his shoulder, all he wants is to kiss her like there's no tomorrow.
Just when he's about to go for it, Shishio shows up, worried.
Yosano's smile lights up like never before, leaving Mamora crushed.
Later that night, Yosano wakes up, and Shishio tries to cheer her up by filling the room with fireflies, hoping she'll have sweet dreams.
Then, he checks her temperature.
Which, let's be real, wouldn't be surprising if she had a fever, considering how flustered she gets every time he gets this close.
The next day, Yosano calls Yuyuka out for tricking her during the trip.
But when Mamora asks what's going on, Yosano just plays it off because deep down, she doesn't want to lose Yuyuka as a friend.
In the end, Yuyuka apologizes and even helps Yosano with clothes and makeup.
So when Shishio sees her hiding behind a curtain, he literally can't help but feel his heart skip a beat.
The teacher, who's always been so chill, now looks at her, all serious and confused.
Because the Yosano standing in front of him isn't the same girl he knew, and that look in her eyes stirs something inside him.
After that, they hang out and have fun.
At one point, Shishio holds her hand to keep her from falling, though honestly, he wishes he never had to let go.
They tell each other how much they love spending time together, and even after letting go of each other's hands, the connection between them is still there.
Yosano even dreams about Shishio turning around to look at her.
And he actually does!
Like they can really read each other's minds.
In that moment, Yosano feels like nothing could make her happier.
But out of nowhere, Mamura surprises her with a kiss.
She's left stunned, totally confused by how this guy, who always seems so distant, is suddenly showing her how deeply he loves her.
Mamura, completely embarrassed, runs off, leaving Yosano feeling terrible, because she knows that if Yuyuka finds out, she'll be furious.
So Yosano decides to keep it to herself.
In fact, Yuyuka even encourages her to confess her feelings to Shishio by text.
But Shishio replies, saying he's really busy right now.
Feeling down, Yosano is about to head home, when Mamura shows up and takes her to this magical, fairy-tale-like spot.
There, she reveals it's actually her birthday, without hesitating.